devdojo.com 2004-10-15

# www.devdojo.com

**This document also outlines the terms and conditons of using devDOJO.com's various sections.**

devDOJO.com is committed to protecting the privacy of users of our site. At devDOJO.com, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. As part of the normal operation of this site, we collect information from you. This Privacy Statement describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information.

information gathered through the devDOJO.com web site  

> Subject to the provisions of this Privacy Statement, devDOJO.com may use accumulated visitor data for various purposes, including but not limited to marketing analysis, service evaluation and planning.
> 
> Currently, devDOJO.com uses personal information as a basis for notifications to users, "opt-in" emails, and in order to implement the terms of the Terms and Conditions of Use governing the website (the "Terms"). User names and email addresses (as well as any additional information that a user may choose to post) are NOT publicly available on the devDOJO.com site.
> 
> devDOJO.com may conduct surveys of other studies of its customer base and usage for marketing and planning purposes. With respect to information collected from such surveys or studies, and in the event that responses are to be publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take the survey and devDOJO.com will disclose only aggregate information regarding its users and not personal information identifying any specific individual. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in cases where surveys allow users to submit written comments, and where devDOJO.com advises users of the possibility of such disclosure at the time they take the survey, devDOJO.com reserves the right to disclose text information provided by any user through such a survey, provided that no personal information identifying that user is disclosed. Participation in such surveys is at the user's option; devDOJO.com does not conduct mandatory surveys. Circumstances under which devDOJO.com would publicly disclose such aggregate information include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with the site population and publicizing overall usage data in press communications.
> 
> Cookies: devDOJO.com may employ "cookies" to provide a user with tailored information. A "cookie" is an element of data that a Service or site, when visited by a user, sends to that user's browser that, in turn, may store that element on the user's hard drive or memory. devDOJO.com uses cookies to better serve users who use our Services; any cookies sent by devDOJO.com will be marked so that they will be accessible only by websites subject to this Privacy Statement. However, at his or her option, and at his or her sole expense and responsibility, any user may block or delete our cookies from his or her hard drive. By disabling cookies, however, certain site features and functionality may no longer work properly, or at all.
> 
> Other Notification: In order to implement or enforce the Terms of devDOJO.com, devDOJO.com may use personal information to contact users on an individual basis.
> 
> At no time, unless law requires such disclosure, disclosure is necessary to aid law enforcement, or a user specifically authorises such disclosure, will devDOJO.com disclose individual user personal information that is not publicly available to unrelated third parties.

links with other sites  

> devDOJO.com contains links to other websites, whether owned or controlled by devDOJO.com affiliates or unrelated third parties. Please note that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from those of devDOJO.com. devDOJO.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any linked website. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of any website you may visit.

choice  

> "Opt-in" Emails: Users may "opt-in" to receive site notifications, newsletters or other information via email. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list will include directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list, or a URL where the user may find such directions.
> 
> Profile Display: These will be displayed to other Members. Again EMail Address Information shall not be disclosed. 

access  

> Users can view their data on their personal profile page. When technically feasible, users are permitted to update their personal information directly through devDOJO.com Service. When such updating service is not technically feasible, devDOJO.com will make reasonable efforts to assist users in updating their personal information.

security  

> To secure site integrity, devDOJO.com employs measures including but not limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and other reasonable security measures and procedures.
> 
> Internal access to users' private and nonpublic personal information is restricted to site administrators and individuals on a need-to-know basis.

enforcement  

> In the event that devDOJO.com becomes aware that site security is compromised or user nonpublic information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to external security attacks, devDOJO.com shall take reasonable measures which it deems appropriate, including but not limited to internal investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities, notwithstanding other provisions of this Statement.
> 
> If devDOJO.com becomes aware that a user's personal information provided to devDOJO.com has been disclosed in a manner not permitted by this Privacy Statement, devDOJO.com shall make reasonable efforts to notify the affected user, as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law, of what information has been disclosed, to the extent that devDOJO.com knows this information.

updates to the terms & conditions  

> To substantively update the Terms & Conditions, we will both post the changed version and its effective date at [http://www.devDOJO.com/index.php?module=content&page=tac](http://www.devdojo.com/index.php?module=content&page=tac). Concurrently with any substantive change to the Privacy Statement, we will email notice of the change to known users at least 15 days in advance (or such shorter or longer time as mandated by law or any judicial or government body).
> 
> Text last modified on 24th October, 2003.

no guarantees  

> While this Privacy Statement expresses devDOJO.com's standards for maintenance of private data, devDOJO.com is not in a position to guarantee that the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, devDOJO.com disclaims any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of private information.

Return to the top of this page.
